{"data":[{"question":"I'll probably go tomorrow.' '________'","a":"So am I","b":"So did I","c":"Neither will I","d":"So will I","answer":"4","explain":"\n- To agree with a positive statement: so + auxiliary\/modal verb + pronoun \n- Change the auxiliary verb related to the original statement","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"I can't remember her name.' '_________'","a":"Neither did I","b":"Neither have I","c":"Nor can I","d":"Nor did I","answer":"3","explain":"- To agree with a negative statement: nor\/neither + auxiliary\/modal verb + pronoun\n\n- Change the auxiliary verb related to the original statement","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"I couldn't cook when I got married.'________","a":"Nor can I","b":"Nor could I","c":"So could I","d":"So did I","answer":"2","explain":"- To agree with a negative statement: nor\/neither + auxiliary\/modal verb + pronoun\n\n- Change the auxiliary verb related to the original statement","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"They couldn't do it'. '________'","a":"So could I","b":"Neither could I","c":"Neither am I","d":"Neither did I","answer":"2","explain":"\n- To agree with a negative statement: nor\/neither + auxiliary\/modal verb + pronoun \n- Change the auxiliary verb related to the original statement","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"He hasn't got a driving licence.' '_________'","a":"So has she","b":"Nor did she","c":"Nor has she","d":"So did she","answer":"3","explain":"\n- To agree with a negative statement: nor\/neither + auxiliary\/modal verb + pronoun \n- Change the auxiliary verb related to the original statement","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"I went very early yesterday morning.' _________","a":"So do I","b":"So did I","c":"So am I","d":"Nor did I","answer":"2","explain":"\n- To agree with a positive statement: so + auxiliary\/modal verb + pronoun \n- Change the auxiliary verb related to the original statement ","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"They can't speak German.' '_________'","a":"So do we","b":"Neither do we","c":"So can we","d":"Nor can we","answer":"4","explain":"- To agree with a negative statement: nor\/neither + auxiliary\/modal verb + pronoun\n\n- Change the auxiliary verb related to the original statement","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"I didn't pass my exam.' '_________'","a":"Neither have I","b":"Neither do I","c":"So did I","d":"Neither did I","answer":"4","explain":"- To agree with a negative statement: nor\/neither + auxiliary\/modal verb + pronoun\n\n- Change the auxiliary verb related to the original statement","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"She is very confused.' '_________'","a":"So I am","b":"So am I","c":"So do I","d":"Nor do I","answer":"2","explain":"\n- To agree with a positive statement: so + auxiliary\/modal verb + pronoun \n- Change the auxiliary verb related to the original statement ","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"I'll probably go next week.' '_________'","a":"Nor will I","b":"So have I","c":"Nor did I","d":"so will I","answer":"4","explain":"\n- To agree with a positive statement: so + auxiliary\/modal verb + pronoun \n- Change the auxiliary verb related to the original statement","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"}]}